{
    "id": "dc7a185f66544b6cb8c6da28b7d452d4",
    "title": "Both, Either And Neither Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6f4f92170b084e398847509c8c306b97",
            "title": "Both, Either And Neither Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She has eaten ....................... of the chops.",
                    "description": "We use both to refer to two people or things. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Alice sends you ........................ her love.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................. of us were ill so we didn't go to work.",
                    "description": "Both means this and that. Either means this or that. Neither means not this and not that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't like ......................... of my Grammar teachers.",
                    "description": "Instead of not....both, we use either. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rahul and Ravi .......................... went to the party.",
                    "description": "Both means this and that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "either",
                        "both",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................... of us play cricket regularly.",
                    "description": "Both means this and that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................... of us went to the party.",
                    "description": "Both expressions are possible here with totally different meanings. Both means this and that. Neither means not this and not that. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Neither",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I couldn't choose between them. I liked them ........................",
                    "description": "Both means this and that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can take ........................... the apple or the orange. You can't have them ......................",
                    "description": "Either is used before the first of two alternatives. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "either, either",
                        "either, both",
                        "both, either"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't think highly of .............................. of them.",
                    "description": "Instead of not...both, we use either.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... swim.",
                    "description": "We do not normally use both...not. Instead we use neither.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both of us cannot",
                        "Neither of us can"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't want ......................................",
                    "description": "Neither is a negative word. We can't use it with not. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "either chocolate or cake",
                        "neither chocolate nor cake",
                        "both chocolate and cake"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}